ABDELMOUGHITH EL AOUMARI

162 Hay El jadid E Ben Guerir • 06-2086-5442 • abdelmoughithelaoumari@gmail.com







PROFILE

Junior Full Stack Developer, 22 years old, highly motivated to learn new skills in the field of computer science to gain more and more experience and to improve my level and qualities to advance my career and become a software development engineer.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Mediaverse | End-of-Year Internship

Apr 2024 - Jun 2024

Developed an online learning and course management system "DAcademy" using the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js) + Next.js.

Rehamna Province | End-of-Studies Internship

Apr 2023 - Jun 2023

• Developed a web platform for human resources management for the Rehamna Province using **Bootstrap** for the front-end and **Laravel** for the back-end.

EST Safi | End-of-Studies Project

Dec 2022 - Jun 2023

 Developed a web platform for digitalizing the internal affairs management of the DAR-TIFL establishment using React JS and Tailwind CSS for the front-end, and Laravel for the backend.

II.S.A.T | Initiation Internship

Jul. 2022 - Aug. 2022

- Developed a stock management web application for the I.S.A.T using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap for the front-end, and PHP for the back-end.
- Gained professional experience by applying my knowledge and developing my observation skills in the workplace.

EDUCATION

Ecole Supérieure de Technologie de SAFI

Oct 2023 - Jun 2024

- · Bachelor's Degree
- Information Systems and Networks Engineering

Ecole Supérieure de Technologie de SAFI

Sep 2021- Jun 2023.

- University Diploma of Technology in Computer Engineering
- · Specialization: Systems and Network Administration

FST Béni-Mellal

1st Year

Sep 2020- Jun 2021

• Specialization: Mathematics-Computer Science-Physics-Chemistry

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Languages: Arabic (fluent), French (B1), English (B1)
- Programming Languages: C, C++, Java (Java SE, Jakarta EE, JavaFX, Hibernate)
- Server-Side: PHP (Laravel), Node.js (ExpressJS)
- Client-Side: React.js, Next.js, Tailwind CSS
- Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, XML, NoSQL (MongoDB)
- Certifications: CCNA 1, CCNA 2, CSE
- Hobbies: Reading, Music, Sports (handball)